

Ferhat Adıbelli

Nationality: Turkish (+90) 5459433435

Date of birth: 15 Nov 1991

Gender: Male

Email address: ferhatadibelli9@gmail.com

Website: https://ferhatadibelli0.github.io/Portfolio/

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ferhat-adibelli-330b27235/

Stackoverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/19093788/ferhat-adibelli

Github:: https://github.com/FerhatAdibelli0

• Address: Gazeteci Hasan Tahsin Cad., No:77, Karabağlar, 35150 İzmir (Turkey)

ABOUT ME

I'm Ferhat. I am from Turkey, I live in Turkey. As a FullStack Developer, I`m very passionate and talented about **ReactJS**, **NextJ S**, **NodeJS**, **ExpressJS**, **MongoDB**, **and MySQL**. I devoted myself to learning, implementing, adapting, and creating throughout my life to build intelligent web apps to help people and improve life quality around the world. As a Web Developer with 14 months of experience able to build web applications from the ground up - information gathering, planning, design, development, testing and delivery, and maintenance.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Science

Turkish Military Academy - Ankara [2010 - 2014]

Field(s) of study: Industrial and Systems Engineering

Final grade: 3.65/4

Master's degree

Gazi Univercity - Ankara [2020 - Current]

Field(s) of study: Computer Forensic

DIGITAL SKILLS

Very good at programming in: HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Boostrap, Jquery, Javascript / React ecosystem: ReactJS, React Router, Redux, Typescript / Backend: NodeJS, Express, socket.io / RESTful api / Git / Github / graphQL / DenoJs / nextjs / Agile (Scrum) / Postman / FireBase / SQL (MySQL) / Basic knowledge of JIRA / Heroku Cloud

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Alme Tech [Feb 2022 - May 2022]

Country: Turkey

Building user interfaces for websites and/or web applications Working with ReactJS, Redux, TypeScript Creating self-contained, reusable, and testable modules and components Writing some end-to-end test on JestJS

Freelancer

Upwork [Oct 2021 – Jan 2022]

Country: Turkey

Upwork helped me find my first job as a Frontend Developer.. It allows me to focus on what is most important for my clients - product and project development.

HONOURS AND AWARDS

ReactJS -- The Complete Guide

Academind

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1UPC_WHLoWUOf9ADO-6|EahHS7nIze|b0/view?usp=sharing

ReactJS -- Web Programming

BTK Academy

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1GIUX8brBrknCW8iVHf1Wg CLPz g7vMr/view?usp=sharing

NodeJS -- The Complete Guide

Academind

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1QxMxt8Wh-j9NF83Sqqsbr8I3E6rRcaqK/view?usp=sharing

Git & Github -- Version Control System

BTK Academy

https://drive.google.com/file/d/17g_fC7fDGiHUKurpCb3R6_6AxzE91zq4/view?usp=sharing

Language Competency

American Culture School

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1HOzdEH-8ytlH_u9XtqXbyaSJIGwNmwDa/view?usp=sharing